jobtestprep.co.uk 2019-05-05

# Privacy Policy and Cookie Information

**Privacy Policy**

**This privacy policy was last updated on August 20 th 2018**

The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to assist you in understanding how we, JobTestPrep, use personal information collected via this website, as well as the choices you can make about how your personal information is used. By submitting your personal information to this website, you are confirming that you have read and understood JobTestPrep's Privacy Policy and that we may use any of the personal information outlined in it. JobTestPrep reserves the right to modify or update this Privacy Policy at any time without prior notice. Any modifications will apply to all information collected by JobTestPrep, including previously collected information.

This privacy policy applies to the website only and does not cover information collected on any third-party sites to which this website links. This privacy policy is part of and must be read in conjunction with the website's Terms and Conditions. If you do not agree to the [Terms and Conditions](https://www.jobtestprep.com/terms) in their entirety, please do not use this website.

**Who we are:**

JobTestPrep is a private online test preparation company, who will be known as the ‘controller’ of the personal data you provide to us.

Company name and registration number: NOAM Institute LTD, 514288711  
Contact info: [c.serv@jobtestprep.co.uk](mailto:c.serv@jobtestprep.co.uk)

**General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) and your rights to privacy:**

JobTestPrep has committed to work with the European Data Protection Authorities to ensure our practices are compliant with the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR). JobTestPrep continually works to maintain GDPR compliance. We understand our role as a controller of EU personal data and take seriously our responsibility to maintain oversight of privacy and security practices and securely process data. We have implemented the required GDPR controls throughout the organization.

You have the right to request more information on what data we have and how we use it, or for us to delete information that you previously shared with us. Should you have any questions, complaints or requests in regards to our privacy policy or practices please contact us at gdpr@jobtestprep.co.uk

If you are not satisfied with our response or believe we are processing your personal data not in accordance with the law you can complain to the Information Commissioner’s Office <https://ico.org.uk/>

**Information visitors provide:**

**Personal information collected on our website**

  1. Visitors who browse our website but do not register and/or have not registered in the past do not have to provide any personal information to browse this website. Any information you do provide (for example in help forms) is optional: Employer name, position, exam type, test date, Email address and phone number.

  2. Visitors who register to our website or have registered in the past agree to provide the following information: Email address and full name. Providing additional information detailed above is optional.

  3. Visitors who make a purchase: Information required by our credit card processor: Full name, email address, billing address, phone number, credit card/ PayPal details, IP Address, and cookies when applicable. Optional information for PrepPack Recommendation and assistance: name of employer, job position, test provider name and test date.

**Other types of information collected on our website**

**What Are "Cookies"**

Cookies and other online tracking technologies are small bits of data or code that are used to identify your browser when you use and interact with our websites and other services. They are often used for remembering your preferences or to remember you’re logged in. Cookies do not contain information that is, in itself, personally identifying; they merely provide certain features, such as tracking sales performance of our affiliates and partners. All visitors are subject to cookies use on the JobTestPrep website by default.

**Which cookies do we use and why?**

**Tracking cookies:** When you visit our website we may collect tracking information, such as your browser type, the type of operating system you use, the name of your Internet service provider, and the pages you visited on the site.

 **Analytics cookies and similar technologies:** These collect information about your use of our websites and apps, and enable us to improve the way they work. These technologies (e.g. Google Analytics) allow us to increase the functionality and user-friendliness of our website and to better tailor our website to your needs. For example, we may want to know how long the average user spends on our website or which pages get the most attention. Information such as this will only be used in aggregate form and will not identify you personally.

**Functional/preference cookies and similar technologies:** These cookies collect information about your choices and preferences and allow us to remember things like your username to make the login process more convenient, and allow us to customise the services you have accessed.  

**Web beacons and tracking pixels:** These are bits of data that count the number of users who access a website or webpage and can also allow us to see if a cookie has been activated. Web beacons used on web pages or in emails allow us to see how successful a page has been, or whether an email message was successfully delivered and read in a marketing campaign. Web beacons are also used to verify any clicks through to links or advertisements contained in emails, which we may use to help us identify which emails are more interesting to you.

**Tracking URLs:** Tracking URLs are a special web link that allows us to measure when a link is clicked on. They are used to help us measure the effectiveness of campaigns.

**How to block or remove cookies on your browser:**

Most modern browsers are set to accept cookies by default, but you can change your settings to notify you when a cookie is being set or updated, or to block cookies altogether. Please consult the “Help” section of your browser. Please note that by blocking any or all cookies, you may not have access to certain features, content, or personalisation available on our websites or apps.

**Test Practice Information**

Registered users who practice any test have a detailed log of their practice which includes:

  * Time Stamp of practice sessions
  * Number of tests viewed
  * Number of tests completed
  * Test score

This information is analysed for the purpose of providing customers with personalised recommendations for successful test preparation. For example, if the JobTestPrep experts see that a customer may have purchased the wrong product for their test, they may refer to the customers test practice information to see which tests the customer has been practicing with. If a customer reaches out for assistance, their previous test practice information enables our experts to give a personalised recommendation for further practice.

Additionally, test practice information may be anonymously collated and analysed to check which tests are required for specific assessments, test providers or institutes, for the purpose of making recommendations to other users.

**How Is My Payment Information Used When I Make a Purchase?**

Our credit card processor BlueSnap was voted as Best E-Commerce Platform / Gateway in CNP Awards. Your information is confidential and protected in compliance with GDPR regulations. The following information is required by BlueSnap in order to process your payment: name, email, address, credit card/ PayPal details, IP Address, and cookies when applicable.

Due to accounting and legal requirements BlueSnap is unable to delete customers’ information. For additional information please contact BlueSnap here: [bluesnap.zendesk.com/hc/en-us/requests/new?ticket_form_id=232328](https://bluesnap.zendesk.com/hc/en-us/requests/new?ticket_form_id=232328)

**What we use your data for**

These are the purposes that we use your data for:

  * Providing this online service and performance of contract following our Terms of Use. 
  * To ensure that you have access to the most relevant practice material personalised for your needs (for example: PrepPack™ Recommendations, PrepPack™ updates and special offers)
  * To ensure your success and satisfaction using our practice material (for example: reviews and satisfaction surveys)
  * Anonymously as a basis for future practice material recommendations
  * Dispatch PrepPack™ recommendations, updates reviews and satisfaction surveys, special offers etc. via newsletters emails with your consent. You may unsubscribe at any time via the unsubscribe link in any email we send you.

**How long we keep your data**

Your information will be kept with us until you notify us that you want it deleted

**Who we share your data with:**

JobTestPrep does not sell or rent any information provided by visitors to any 3rd party. 

We work with the following third party processors who each uphold by the GDPR regulations and have Data Protection Adendums in place to protect the customers data:

Autopilot, Bluesnap, Calendly, Freshdesk, Gmetrix, Google Tag Manager, iDevAffiliates, Inline Manual, Jotform, OptinMonster, RIVS InterviewStream, Twilio, Umbraco, Yotpo, Zapier. You may contact us for more information on how your information is processed through these companies, for contact information or for data requests.

JobTestPrep may disclose information if we in good faith believe that such action is necessary to (1) comply with the law or with legal processes; (2) protect and defend our rights and property; (3) protect against misuse or unauthorized use of the website; or (4) protect the personal safety, property, or rights of our users or the public.

**Children's Online Privacy Protection Act**

No one under the age of 13 should provide any personal information. In general, JobTestPrep does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. If in limited circumstances we do knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13, we will do so only with verified parental consent prior to collection. In the event that we learn that we have collected information from a child under the age of 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete this information from our database as quickly as possible. If you believe the website has any information about an individual under the age of 13, please contact us at [c.serv@jobtestprep.co.uk](mailto:c.serv@jobtestprep.c).
